I don't think I'm overstating him when I
say that the last two seasons of anime
说最后两个季节的动漫
were some of the best we've seen in
是我们见过的最好的一些
years
年份
so spring 2019 has a lot to live up to
所以春季2019有很多不辜负
so what could possibly be carrying the
什么可能携带的
season well looking at the chart it
季节很好看图表吧
should be pretty obvious I mean because
应该是非常明显的我的意思是因为
this season we have the one the only
本赛季我们有一个唯一的
Mira tights it's a show about girls
Mira紧身衣是一个关于女孩的节目
wearing wet tights it's a show about
穿着湿紧身衣， 这是一个表演
girls wearing wet myself one hand I
女孩一只手湿着我
somehow find myself watching the second
不知何故发现自己在看第二个
anime suppository seen in back-to-back
动漫栓剂背靠背看到
seasons of some guy trying to get with
一些人试图与之相处的季节
his teacher in that's the best part the
他在老师的最好的部分
anime and on the other on debating
动漫，另一方面辩论
whether it's worth turning this off and
是否值得关闭它
treasuring the small bit of dignity
珍惜一点点尊严
I still have wretch shut up shop this is
我还可怜虫关门了，这是
the best part this is the best part this
最好的部分， 这是最好的部分
is later show in animes new genre I
随后显示animes新流派我
can't believe it's not hentai and I mean
我不敢相信它不是无尽的
I can't be the only one noticing
我不可能是唯一注意到的人
nowadays how the line between anime
时下如何动漫之间的界限
plots and hentai plots is slowly
情节和无尽的情节正在缓慢
blurring at this point you can basically
在这一点上模糊你基本上可以
see you or a hentai tags you can add to
看到你或你可以添加的无尽标签
an anime so why the hell not let's see
一个动漫，所以为什么不让我们看到
how many tags we can collect this season
我们本季可以收集多少标签
and see how hentai anime has gotten I
看看无尽的动漫是如何得到我的
swear to god out of me you better not do
向上帝发誓我了，你最好别做
it I don't need this shit in my anime
我在动漫中不需要这个狗屎
right now nobody asked to see some ugly
现在没有人要求看到一些丑陋
sweaty ogres bang a bunch of innocent
满身是汗的食人魔砰的一声无辜
lollies being heap doing it anyway don't
无论如何， lollies 正在堆着它
do it don't fucking do it if I see one
如果我看到一个，那就不要他妈的去做
more big fat fucking jungus when I leave
我离开时更加大胖他妈的琼花
don't do it oh my god he's beautiful I
不要这样做哦我的上帝他很漂亮我
have the biggest nostalgia boner right
拥有最大的怀旧之情
now it's like an erection Strayed in my
现在它就像是在我身上迷失的勃起
childhood
童年
you crying I'm not crying these are just
你哭了我不哭这些只是
the pre-cum of my soul man what time
什么时候我的灵魂人的前暨
period are we living in right now it
期间内，我们生活在现在这
feels weird that it's 2019 and one of
感到奇怪，它是2019年和其中之一
the biggest shows this season is fruits
本赛季最大的节目是水果
baskets but in this age of new season
篮子，但在这个新赛季的时代
announcements and remakes let it sink in
公告和重拍让它沉入其中
that your favorite order anime is
你最喜欢的订单动漫是
probably more likely to get another
可能更容易得到另一
season or remake now than it did when it
季节或翻拍现在的确要比它的时候
aired like a decade ago so that's right
像十年前一样播出，这是对的
boys the dream isn't dead yet you know
男孩，梦想没有死，但你知道
what I actually wanted to give a quick
我真的想快速给出什么
shout out to China because I saw this
因为我看到了这一点而向中国大喊大叫
clip the other day and the Chinese made
前几天和中国制造的
anime and this is by far the best cg
动漫，这是迄今为止最好的cg
crowds I've seen I didn't even notice it
人群我见过我甚至没有注意到它
was ceg until someone pointed it out and
在CEG直到有人指出了这一点，并
if you really concentrate it does look a
如果你真的专注，它看起来确实如此
bit stiff it's not perfect but dear Lord
有点僵硬，这不完美，但亲爱的主
we're finally making strides I thought
我想，我们终于取得了进步
we were making progress I thought we
我想我们正在取得进步
were making progress
正在取得进展
hey it's a show called demon slayer
嘿，这是一个叫恶魔杀手的节目
about a guy who slays demons and would
关于一个杀死恶魔的人会
you look at that it's been an entire
你看，这是一个完整的
episode of no one's been violently
一集都没有人暴力
assaulted so don't have to add any more
殴打所以不必再添加了
suspect tags but of God say you folks
可疑的标签，但上帝说你们的人
more have done it again and I was sold
更多人再次这样做了，我被卖掉了
seeing this absolutely gorgeous
看到这绝对华丽
beautifully directed dynamic little
精美的导演动态小
sister on a serious note though is cool
妹妹虽然很酷，但还是很认真
to see another shounen jump title
看到另一个shounen跳冠军
getting the premium treatment from you
从你那里获得优质治疗
photo at this time and once again I mean
在这个时候的照片， 我的意思是再一次
it's you photo it looks like the action
它是你的照片，看起来像是动作
scenes are exhilarating integrating the
场景令人振奋，整合了
trademark ufotable CG and dynamic camera
商标ufotable CG和动态相机
and I'm just happy to hear Yuki Kaji are
而且我很高兴听到Yuki Kaji
all of them again even if it sounds
所有的人再次，即使它听起来
eerily similar to her work on fate/zero
与她在命运/归零方面的工作非常相似
and Kara no Kyoukai and that's not a
和Kara no Kyoukai，那不是
complaint I swear cuz I say the same
投诉我发誓因为我说同样的话
thing about Sour no but come on it's
关于酸的事情没有，但是来吧
sour no everything's better with a sour
酸味没有一切都带有酸味更好
no drop it feels like ages since we last
自从我们上次以来，感觉就像年龄一样
heard him so you know what to prove my
听到他，所以你知道要证明什么
point about sour no drops here's a
关于酸不点滴在这里是一个
dramatic slow zoom of a waffle falling
华夫饼飘落的戏剧性慢变焦
over to the sound of the ape Titan theme
猿人泰坦主题的声音
there he gone more like barely gone for
在那里，他更像是勉强走了
my memory no seriously this show was so
我的记忆没有认真对待这个节目
painful he forgets why I really don't
痛苦的他忘了我为什么不这样做
have much to say about it oh I've seen
有太多的话要说，它哦，我见过
enough anime to know where this is going
足够的动漫来了解这是怎么回事
haha checkmate officer you can't arrest
哈哈将军官你不能逮捕
me if I'm already arrested look let's be
我， 如果我已经被捕，那就让我们成为
honest when you see a character design
当你看到角色设计时诚实
like this paired with the words 800 year
像这样配对800年的话
old fox girl your first reaction is
老狐狸女孩你的第一反应是
probably to think something dodgy is up
可能会认为狡猾的事情正在发生
and hope to god that is not your penis
希望上帝不是你的阴茎
but dear Lord the helpful Fox sang
亲爱的福克斯 亲爱的主唱
cosine is just one wholesome ass show
余弦只是一个健康的屁股秀
watching an episode of this is like the
看一集就像这样
real-life equivalent of eating a sense
现实生活相当于吃感
of being you're just watching a
因为你只是在看一个
stressed-out overworked salary man being
压力过大的薪水男子正在
pampered by a fox lolly and it's the
受到狐狸棒棒糖的呵护，这就是它
closest to real life HP recovery you're
最接近现实生活HP恢复你
gonna get this is like fanservice for
会得到这就像粉丝服务
the Soul I mean just having a chasm hey
灵魂我的意思是只有一个鸿沟嘿
I heard you liked Issei KY so it took an
我听说你喜欢Issei KY所以它花了一个
e say Chi and he say Chi nice a kind and
E假定志和他说， 智漂亮一种和
E say Chi then II sake I ve say kind to
E说Chi然后II清酒我说得很好
another
另一个
Issei Chi is this ISA kind enough for
Issei Chi对于这​​种ISA来说足够了
you I really didn't think I'd like this
你我真的不认为我喜欢这个
as much as I do
像我这样做
I lied I like this exactly as much as I
我骗我喜欢这正是像我
thought I would but didn't want to admit
以为我会， 但不想承认
to myself I mean it's just a glorified
对我自己，我的意思是它只是一个美化
Eastlake I fanfiction who would have
Eastlake我很喜欢谁
thought that seeing Eastlake I character
以为看到Eastlake我的性格
x'b and with each other could be so damn
x'b和彼此可能真是太该死了
enjoyable cause you got all your
愉快， 因为你得到了所有的
favorite characters here Kazuma ein
最喜欢的角色Kazumaein
summer hot qua Amelia
夏天炎热的阿米莉亚
C brew whoever this is truckin oh there
C酿造谁这是卡车哦那里
he is
他是
there's my boy again of course the
当然还有我的男孩
season wouldn't be complete without at
如果没有，赛季就不会完整
least one new ISA Kai and I've got to
至少有一个新的ISA凯和我必须这样做
give it to Kendra in the margo sea while
把它送到margo海的肯德拉
most sa car nowadays strive to have at
如今大多数汽车都力求拥有
least one original hook or premise
至少一个原始的钩子或前提
before diving to every other generic sa
在潜入其他所有通用sa之前
kike engine imago is completely original
kike引擎意象是完全原创的
in its complete unoriginal 'ti you may
在它完整的非原创'你可能
be thinking how it's possible to make a
正在思考如何制作一个
generic anime that is more generic than
通用动漫比通用动漫更通用
the most generic ISA Kai there is you
最通用的ISAKai就是你
add a magic harem high school into it
加入一个神奇的后宫高中
yeah it's an e sake high magic harem
是的，这是一个高魔法后宫
high school that's right people we have
高中，这是我们合适的人
reached new heights of generic Ness
达到了通用Ness的新高度
what look let's be honest though if you
如果你这么看我们应该说实话
lease a high-power fantasy trash like me
租用像我这样的高功率幻想垃圾
you're gonna find yourself watching it
你会发现自己在看它
anyway for reasons you don't know why
无论如何因为你不知道原因
because from the premise to the studio
因为从工作室的前提
to the staff members there is absolutely
该工作人员也绝对
nothing noteworthy about this shut era
这个关闭时代没什么值得注意的
manga sensei and domestic girlfriend
漫画老师和国内女友
it can't be I found him my god I didn't
它不可能我发现他是我的上帝我没有
think he was real he's learned the
认为他是真实的，他已经学会了
forbidden technique it's the man who's
禁止的技术是男人的
mastered ultra incest on today's episode
在今天的剧集中掌握了超乱伦
of my social anxiety can't be this cute
我的社交焦虑不可能这么可爱
we have hitori Bochy detailing the
我们有hitori Bochy详细介绍了
adventures of a precious 14 year old
一个宝贵的14岁的冒险
girl as she awkwardly stumbles through
女孩， 因为她笨拙地绊倒了
making some tour my dad geez aka it's
做一些游览我爸爸geez又名它
basically just what ammo II honestly
基本上只是弹药II老实说
though this is just fucking adorable
虽然这 仅仅是他妈的可爱
with so many hashtag mood hashtag
有这么多的标签心情标签
relatable moments it's almost as if this
相关的时刻几乎就像这样
show is actually about if I was
如果是的话，节目实际上是关于
reincarnated as a socially awkward
转世为社交尴尬
middle school anime girl though that
中学动漫女孩虽然那样
just makes it sound like a nice acai or
只是让它听起来像一个很好的acai或
something all right what do we go next
有事没事我们怎么去下一个
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]
I'm gay now where do I even start with
我现在是同性恋，我甚至从哪里开始
this one what tags this is even belong
这个标签甚至属于什么标签
to so welcome to the latest drug-induced
如此欢迎最新的药物诱导
brain fart of Kunihiko Ichi Hara whose
Kunihiko IchiHara的脑屁
works include the likes of Mara Roux
作品包括MaraRoux等
penguindrum and revolutionary girl utena
penguindrum 和革命女孩utena
which if you're familiar with will give
如果你熟悉的话会给予
you a much better sense of what you're
你一个更好的你是什么感觉
getting into than anything I could save
进入比我能保存的任何东西
right now I don't think it's actually
现在 ，我不认为它实际上
possible to sum up this anime in the
可以总结一下这个动漫
single sentence but I'm gonna damn well
单句， 但我会好的
try anyway
试试吧
imagine if Monica tree and URI and ice
想象一下如果莫妮卡树和URI和冰
had a persona flavored frog baby that
有一个人格味的青蛙宝宝
was anally conceived in Bollywood you're
你是宝莱坞人想的
watching three boys get transforms two
看着三个男孩变形两个
frogs or cappers when they get eaten
吃青蛙或封盖机
asked first by another Kappa as they end
当他们结束时，另一个Kappa首先问道
people's anuses in order to consume
人们的肛门才能消费
their inner desire they kinda like the
他们的内心渴望有点像
phantom thieves except instead of
幽灵小偷除了代替
inducing a change of heart they just eat
引起他们刚吃 的心脏改变
ass it's about eating ass
屁股是关于吃屁股
yes someone's finally made an anime
是的，有人终于制作了动漫
about eating the Kumar's work as famous
关于吃Kumar的作品而闻名
being very out there on a surface level
是非常那里 在表面水平
requiring you to dig through as many
要求你挖掘尽可能多的东西
layers to come to your own conclusion
层来得出你自己的结论
which this definitely is buzz current
这肯定是嗡嗡声当前
the appeal of it I mean you look at
它的吸引力我的意思是你看
something like this and maybe you see a
像这样的东西，也许你看到了
message about hidden desires it's
关于隐藏欲望的消息
brought to the lens of traditional
带到了传统的镜头
Japanese folklore with the side of
日本民间传说的一面
homoeroticism set in the technologically
同性恋主义在技​​术上设定
red lights modern day or you might just
红灯现代或你可能只是
see Avengers endgame spoilers I would
看复仇者看到破坏者我会
say Oh enjoyed it
说哦很享受
but that would imply my brain had
但这意味着我的大脑已经拥有了
rationalized the experience to something
使经验合理化
close enough to resembling a coherent
足够接近， 像一个连贯的
thought
思想
I know powerfully through yakuman what's
我通过yakuman有力地了解了什么
your winger EEMA
你的边锋EEMA
okay oh boy he knew I was coming one
好吧哦，男孩， 他知道我要来了
punch man is back with a new studio new
拳击男子回来了新的工作室
staff members and a production schedule
工作人员和生产计划
that seems to have set itself on fire
这似乎让自己着火了
all the signs were pointing to this
所有的迹象都指向了这一点
being an absolute tragedy so was it the
是一个绝对的悲剧所以它是
biggest disaster to ever grace our anime
我们动漫的最大灾难
community nah it was um it was okay
社区不，这是没关系的
honestly this probably was the most okay
说实话，这可能是最好的
return I've seen it's really not as bad
回来我看到它真的没那么糟糕
as people are making it out to be but
正如人们正在努力的那样
when you're coming off one of the
当你离开其中一个
greatest showcase of action animation in
最伟大的动作动画 展示
the last decade to some of the most
过去十年中的一些最多
bog-standard averaged fight scenes you
沼泽标准平均战斗场景你
can find anywhere else yeah it's gonna
可以找到任何其他地方是的它会
be a bit of a disappointment but it has
是有点失望，但它有
best girl yes this is canon best girl
最好的女孩是的，这是佳能最好的女孩
there is no debate this time so I'll
这次没有辩论，所以我会
still probably watch it anyway cause
仍然可能无论如何都要看它
animation aside the new character
除了新角色之外的动画
designs don't even bother me that much
设计甚至不会打扰我
even if they've given saitama's bald
即使他们给了saitama的秃头
head this weird shiny gradient blush
这个奇怪的闪亮渐变腮红
thing which I've know I've seen in anime
我知道我在动漫中看过的东西
before but I can't quite put my finger
之前， 但我不能完全放手指
on it wait a minute yes yes yes yes yes
在它等待一分钟是是是是是是
do you that it's a familiar sound war is
你认为这是一场熟悉的声音战争吗？
coming
未来
another long romantic comedy with one
另一部长篇浪漫喜剧
male lead another show with many girls
男性带领许多女孩的另一个节目
worth protecting so pick your side
值得保护， 所以选择你的一面
soldier there'll be a long and arduous
士兵那将是一个漫长而艰巨的过程
battle and whoever wins you won't be
战斗，无论谁赢了你都不会
forgetting it any time soon because
很快忘记它，因为
remember soldiers wars may come and go
记得士兵的战争可能来去匆匆
but salt remains eternal I've picked my
但盐仍然是永恒的，我已经选择了我的
corner all right I'm just gonna set up
好吧我会安排好的
camp here on Team sensei cuz I think
我认为，在这支队伍中，我可以参加
between this domestic girlfriend and the
这个国内的女朋友和之间
previous teacher show I am ready to
以前的老师秀我准备好了
declare that we have entered the dawn of
宣称我们已经进入了曙光
a new age the era of the Emoto is dead
一个新的时代，Emoto的时代 已经死了
it's time to start the age of the tills
是时候开始收割的时代了
that's right teachers I'd like to feed
那是我想要喂养的合适的老师
all my love and attention to you because
所有我对你的爱和关注因为
teachers are hardworking humans just
老师们只是勤劳的人
trying to harness and is it wrong to
试图利用并且是错误的
just want to sensei you can smile with
只是希望老师可以用微笑
the pure happiness she deserves okay you
纯粹的幸福，她值得你好吗
got it yeah yeah I think I got it all
得到它是啊是啊我想我得到了一切
right just follow
正好跟随
my lead okay today is gonna be the day
我 今天 铅还好是会到来的那一天
that I never throw it back sometimes all
我从来不扔回去，有时所有
it takes is one episode I went to
这是我去过的一集
Carroll and chooses there with quite a
卡罗尔与相当有选择
lot of hype as someone who really loves
作为一个真正喜欢的人，大量的炒作
anime about music and this being the
关于音乐的动漫，这就是它
latest outing of bones and Shinichiro
最新的骨头和Shinichiro
Watanabe who if he didn't know is the
渡边谁，如果他不知道是
director behind shows like Cowboy Bebop
像Cowboy Bebop这样的导演背后的导演
samurai Champloo zankyou no terror
武士Champloo zankyou没有恐怖
us-based bandy kids on the slope so yeah
我们在斜坡上的乐队孩子是的，所以是的
basically a nobody
基本上没人
even with that hype this first episode
即使是第一集的炒作
floored me aside from the stunning
让我惊艳不已
visuals it did pretty much everything a
视觉效果它确实几乎一切
first episode needed to do it takes
第一集需要这样做
similar beats of some of the great music
一些伟大音乐的类似节拍
anime of the past like Beck and Nana
像贝克和娜娜 一样过去的动漫
you've got a completely original and
你有一个完全原创的
interesting setting in Mars of all
火星中有趣的环境
places in a future where culture is
在未来的地方文化
produced by AI and to top it off you've
人工智能制作并完成你的工作
got this one scene where the two girls
得到这两个女孩的场景
are trying to figure out this song and
正在试图找出这首歌
there's this beautiful little moment
这是一个美好的小时刻
when they're just fumbling around out of
当他们刚刚走出来的时候
sync jamming together for the first time
第一次同步干扰
before slowly piecing it together and
前慢慢拼凑一起，并
then there's a moment where it just
然后就是片刻
clicks and I just felt this chill run
点击和我只是觉得这个寒意运行
down my spine
我的脊椎
[Music]
[音乐]
that's all it took for me to fall in
这就是我所需要的全部内容
love with this show it could go to shit
喜欢这个节目它可能会变得糟透了
but I am already invested my only regret
但我已经投入了我唯一的遗憾
is that is behind Netflix license jail
这是Netflix许可证监狱的 背后
meaning not many people are talking
意思是没有多少人在说话
about it but I'm probably gonna wait for
关于它，但我可能会等待
the full release after this anyway
无论如何，在此之后完全释放
because this is a show that I'm gonna
因为这是一个我要去的节目
need to marathon so aside from that it's
需要马拉松所以除了 它的
fucking great and absolutely nothing can
他妈的很棒，绝对没有什么可以
possibly go hey guys hope you enjoyed
可能会嘿嘿家伙希望你喜欢
the video thank you very much they too
视频非常感谢你们
careless just wean us Walt o supreme
粗心只是让我们失去了沃尔特至尊
sayin Nicolas Tatum sisters one zero
说尼古拉斯塔图姆姐妹一分零
zero eight six grant fields and everyone
零八个赠款领域和每个人
else my patreon to helping support me
别的我patreon 帮助支持我
for this month and making this video
这个月和制作这个视频
possible
可能
you know itself like talking about
你知道自己喜欢谈论
anything else I wanted to give an extra
我想要额外的东西
thanks to them today because if you
今天感谢他们，因为如果你
didn't know a few days ago my entire
前几天我不知道我的全部
channels just suddenly got demonetised
频道突然被恶化了
by YouTube which was yeah bit of a scare
通过YouTube，这有点吓人
luckily first you or I managed to get it
幸运的是， 首先你或我设法得到它
back pretty quickly but it was kind of a
回来很快，但它有点像
wake-up call and made me really thankful
当头棒喝，让我真的很感谢
that I do have this safety net in case
我确实有这个安全网以防万一
unli something like this happens again
unli这样的事情再次发生
and I mean yeah I guess it goes to show
我的意思是，我想它会显示出来
that it could really happen to anyone no
它真的可能发生在任何人身上
matter how big or small you are in this
无论是大还是小，你在这
anime community anyway though that's it
尽管如此，动漫社区也是如此
for me
为了我
I've been geared up and I'll see you all
我已经作好准备 ，我会看到你的所有
next time
下次